<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>tanglet.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Tanglet</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Tanglet</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Tanglet</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Tanglet</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Tanglet</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Tanglet</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Tanglet</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Tanglet</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Tanglet</name>
  <name xml:lang="ms">Tanglet</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Tanglet</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Tanglet</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Tanglet</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Tanglet</name>
  <summary>Single player variant of Boggle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Variant d'un jugador de Boggle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Varianta hry Boggle pro jednoho hráče</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Einzelspielervariante von Boggle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Single player παραλλαγή του Boggle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Variante de un jugador de Boggle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Variante de Boggle en mode simple joueur</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">A Boggle egyjátékos változata</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Boggle žaidimo variantas vienam žaidėjui</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ms">Varian pemain tunggal Boggle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Eenpersoonsversie van Boggle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Jednoosobowa wersja gry Boggle.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Uma variante do jogo Parole</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Variantă de joc Boggle într-un singur jucător</summary>

  <description>
    <p>Tanglet is a single player word finding game based on Boggle. The object of the game is to list as many words as you can before the time runs out. There are several timer modes that determine how much time you start with, and if you get extra time when you find a word.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Tanglet és un joc de recerca de paraules per a un jugador basat en Boggle. L'objectiu del joc és llistar tantes paraula com pugueu abans de que s'acabi el temps. Hi ha distintes modalitats que determinen el temps que disposes, i si aconsegueixes temps extra per a cada paraula trobada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Tanglet je hra o hledání slov postavená na Boogle. Předmětem hry je sestavení seznamu tolika slov, kolik můžete, předtím než uplyne čas. Pro časomíru je tu několik režimů, jež určují, kolik času máte na začátku, a jestli dostanete, když najdete slovo, nějaký čas navíc. </p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Tanglet ist ein Buchstabenrätsel für eine Person, das auf Boggle basiert. Ziel des Spiels ist es, so viele Wörter wie möglich zu finden bevor die Zeit abläuft. Es gibt mehrere Spielmodi, die bestimmen, wieviel Bedenkzeit Sie am Spielanfang haben und ob die Bedenkzeit verlängert wird, wenn Sie ein Wort finden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Tanglet είναι ένα single player παιχνίδι εύρεσης λέξεων πού βασίζεται στο Boggle. Το αντικείμενο του παιχνιδιού είναι η δημιουργία λιστών με όσες λέξεις γίνεται, πριν τελειώσει ο χρόνος. Υπάρχουν αρκετές λειτουργίες χρονοδιακόπτη που καθορίζουν με πόσο χρόνο μπορείτε να ξεκινήσετε  και αν μπορείτε να πάρετε επιπλέον χρόνο όταν βρείτε μια λέξη.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Tanglet es un juego de buscar palabras de un sólo jugador basado en Boggle. El objeto del juego es listar tantas palabras como puedas antes de que se acabe el tiempo. Hay distintos modos que determinan con cuánto tiempo inicias, y si obtienes tiempo extra por cada palabra encontrada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Tanglet est un jeu de recherche de mots, en mode simple joueur, basé sur le fameux Boggle. L'objectif de ce jeu est de lister autant de mots que possible avant la fin du temps imparti. Plusieurs modes de minuterie sont proposés. Ils déterminent le temps de départ et le temps supplémentaire accordé lorsqu'un mot a été trouvé. </p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Tanglet yra žodžių ieškojimo žaidimas paremtas Boggle. Žaidimo tikslas yra, prieš pasibaigiant laikui, išvardinti kuo daugiau žodžių. Yra kelios laikmačio veiksenos, kurios nustato, kiek laiko duota žaidimo pradžioje, ir ar bus pridedamas laikas, esant teisingam spėjimui.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Tanglet merupakan permainan mencari perkataan seorang pemain berasaskan Boggle. Objektif permainan adalah untuk menyenaraikan sebanyak mungkin perkataan sebelum masa tamat. Terdapat beberapa mod pemasa yang menentukan berapakah masa mula anda, dan jika anda mendapat masa tambahan bila anda berjaya mencari perkataan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Tanglet is een eenpersoonsversie van een woordzoekspel gebaseerd op Boggle. Het doel van het spel is om zo veel mogelijk woorden op te schrijven voordat de tijd voorbij is. Er zijn verschillende tijdmodi die bepalen met hoe veel tijd je begint of wat voor een tijdbonus je krijgt als je een woord vind.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Tanglet jest jednosobową grą polegająca na wyszukiwaniu słów, opartą na grze Boggle. Celem gry jest wyszukanie tak wielu słów jak to możliwe przed upływem czasu. Istnieje kilka trybów gry, które determinują to z jaką ilością czasu zaczynasz i czy uzyskujesz dodatkowy czas za znalezienie słowa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Tanglet é um jogo de um só jogador para encontrar palavras, baseado no jogo Parole. O objetivo do jogo é encontrar o máximo de palavras possível antes do tempo se esgotar. Existem vários modos de temporizador que determinam o tempo com que se começa e se se obtém tempo extra quando se encontra uma palavra.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Tanglet este un joc de găsit cuvinte, într-un singur jucător, bazat pe Boggle. Obiectivul jocului este de a lista cît mai multe cuvinte înainte de expirarea timpului. Există mai multe moduri de temporizare care determină cu cît de mult timp începeţi, şi dacă aveţi timp suplimentar atunci cînd găsiţi un cuvînt.</p>

    <p>You can join letters horizontally, vertically, or diagonally in any direction to make a word, so as long as the letters are next to each other on the board. However, you can not reuse the same letter cells in a single word. Also, each word must be at least three letters on a normal board, and four letters on a large board.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Podeu unir lletres horitzontalment, verticalment o en diagonal en qualsevol direcció per a formar una paraula, sempre i quan les lletres estiguin contigües en el tauler. Però no podeu fer servir més d'una vegada la mateixa cel·la en una paraula. També, cada paraula ha de tenir tres lletres en el tauler normal o quatre lletres en el tauler gran.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Písmena můžete v kterémkoli směru, abyste udělali slovo, spojovat vodorovně, svisle nebo úhlopříčně tak dlouho, dokud jsou písmena na hrací desce vedle sebe. Nicméně nemůžete v jednom slově znovu použít to samé písmeno, když už jste je použili. Každé slovo také musí sestávat z alespoň tří písmen na obyčejné desce a ze čtyř na velké desce.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Sie können Buchstaben senkrecht, waagrecht, oder diagonal in beliebiger Richtung verbinden, um ein Wort zu bilden, solange die Buchstaben auf dem Spielbrett aneinander angrenzen. Sie dürfen aber nicht dasselbe Buchstabenfeld mehrmals in einem Wort verwenden. Außerdem muss jedes Wort auf einem normalgroßen Spielbrett mindestens aus drei Buchstaben bestehen, und auf einem großen Spielbrett mindestens aus vier Buchstaben.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Μπορείτε να συντάψετε γράμματα οριζόντια, κάθετα, ή διαγώνια σε οποιαδήποτε κατεύθυνση , μόσο όσο τα γράμματα είναι δίπλα το ένα στο άλλο. Ωστόσο, δεν μπορείτε να χρησιμοποιήσετε ξανά το ίδιο γράμμα σε μια ενιαία λέξη. Επίσης, κάθε λέξη πρέπει να αποτελείται από τουλάχιστον τρία γράμματα σε έναν μικρό και τέσσερα γράμματα σε ένα μεγάλο πίνακα.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Puedes unir letras horizontalmente, verticalmente, o diagonalmente en cualquier dirección para formar una palabra, siempre y cuando las letras están contiguas en el tablero. Sin embargo, no puedes reusar una misma celda en una sola palabra. También, cada palabra debe contener al menos tres letras en un tablero normal, o cuatro letras en un tablero grande. </p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Vous pouvez relier des lettres horizontalement, verticalement ou en diagonale dans n'importe quelle direction pour former un mot, du moment que les lettres soient à côté l'une de l'autre sur le plateau. Cependant, vous ne pouvez pas réutiliser les mêmes cellules de lettres en un seul mot. En outre, chaque mot doit être composé d'au moins trois lettres pour un plateau normal, et de quatre lettres pour un grand plateau.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Kad atspėtumėte žodį, galite jungti raides horizontaliai, vertikaliai, arba pagal įstrižainę bet kuria kryptimi, tol, kol raidės yra viena šalia kitos. Tačiau negalite naudoti to pačio raidės langelio vienam žodžiui. Be to, normalioje plokštėje kiekviename žodyje turi būti bent trys raidės, o didelėje plokštėje bent keturios raidės.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Anda boleh gabungkan huruf secara menegak, melintang, atau mengikut pepenjuru pada mana-mana arah untuk membentuk perkataan, selagi huruf bersebelahan diantara satu sama lain. Akan tetapi, anda tidak boleh guna sel huruf yang sama dalam satu perkataan. Selain itu, setiap perkataan mesti sekurang-kurangnya tiga huruf dalam papan biasa, dan empat huruf dalam papan besar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Je kunt letters horizontaal, verticaal of diagonaal met elkaar verbinden om een woord te maken mits de letters naast elkaar liggen op het bord. Je kunt het letterblokje niet meer dan een keer gebruiken. Verder moet ieder woord minstens 3 letters zijn op een normaal bord en 4 op een groot bord</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Litery możesz łączyć w słowa; pionowo, posiomo, lub po skosie, w dowolnym kierunku, dopóty dopóki litery na planszy występują obok siebie. Aczkolwiek nie możesz użyć dwa razy tej samej komórki z literą. Dodatkowo każde słowo musi się składać z co najmniej trzech liter na planszy o normalnych rozmiarach i czterech liter na dużej planszy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Pode-se juntar letras na horizontal, vertical e diagonal em qualquer direção para formar uma palavra, desde que as letras estejam logo na casa seguinte do tabuleiro. No entanto, não se pode tornar a usar uma letra de uma casa já selecionada numa só palavra. Além disso, cada palavra tem de ter pelo menos 3 letras num tabuleiro normal, e 4 letras num tabuleiro grande.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Puteţi alătura litere orizontal, vertical, sau în diagonală, în orice direcţie pentru a face un cuvînt, atîta timp cît literele sînt una lîngă alta pe tablă. Cu toate acestea, nu aveţi posibilitatea să reutilizaţi aceleaşi celule literă într-un singur cuvînt. De asemenea, fiecare cuvînt trebuie să fie de cel puţin trei litere pe o tablă obişnuită şi patru litere pe o tablă mare.</p>
  </description>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gottcode.org/tanglet/screenshots/appdata.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://gottcode.org/tanglet/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gottcode.org/tanglet/bugs/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://gottcode.org/tip/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://www.transifex.com/projects/p/tanglet/</url>

  <developer_name>Graeme Gott</developer_name>
  <update_contact>graeme@gottcode.org</update_contact>

  <translation type="qt">tanglet</translation>

  <provides>
    <binary>tanglet</binary>
  </provides>

  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>

  <releases>
    <release version="1.5.3" date="2018-07-20">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Automatic high DPI support</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.5.2" date="2018-05-29">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Race condition when checking for canceled games</li>
          <li>FIXED: Crash if window closed while optimizing word list</li>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
          <li>Extra warnings only shown in debug build</li>
          <li>Improved Linux deployment</li>
          <li>Improved macOS deployment</li>
          <li>Improved Windows deployment</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Portuguese</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
